University of Connecticut, Board of Trustees Records 1987.0007
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series I: Minutes, 1881-
  - pp. 7015 - 7016, 1981 October 7 (Box 34:, Folder 380)
  - pp. 7017 - 7025, 1981 November 13 (Box 34:, Folder 381)
    - Attachments (Box 34:, Folder 382)
    - Attachments (Box 35:, Folder 383 - 384)
  - pp. 7026 - 7035, 1982 January 8 (Box 35:, Folder 385)
    - Attachments (Box 35:, Folder 386 - 387)
  - pp. 7036 - 7039, 1982 February 11 (Box 35:, Folder 388)
    - Attachments (Box 35:, Folder 389 - 391)
  - pp. 7040 - 7047, 1982 March 12 (Box 36:, Folder 392)
    - Attachments (Box 36:, Folder 393 - 394)
  - pp. 7048 - 7053, 1982 April 16 (Box 36:, Folder 395)
    - Attachments (Box 36:, Folder 396 - 397)
  - pp. 7054 - 7060, 1982 May 21 (Box 36:, Folder 398)
    - Attachments (Box 36:, Folder 399 - 400)
  - pp. 7061 - 7066, 1982 June 9 (Box 37:, Folder 401)
    - Attachments (Box 37:, Folder 402 - 403)
  - pp. 7065 - 7066, 1982 June 23 (Box 37:, Folder 404)
    - Attachments (Box 37:, Folder 405)
  - pp. 7067 - 7074, 1982 July 9 (Box 37:, Folder 406)
    - Attachments (Box 37:, Folder 407 - 408)
  - pp. 7075 - 7081, 1982 September 10 (Box 37:, Folder 409)
    - Attachments (Box 37:, Folder 410)
    - Attachments (Box 38:, Folder 411 - 412)
  - pp. 7082 - 7084, 1982 October 8 (Box 38:, Folder 413)
    - Attachments (Box 38:, Folder 414)
  - pp. 7085 - 7093, 1982 November 12 (Box 38:, Folder 415)
    - Attachments (Box 38:, Folder 416 - 417)
  - pp. 7094 - 7100, 1983 January 13 (Box 38:, Folder 418)
    - Attachments (Box 38:, Folder 419 - 420)
  - pp. 7101 - 7104, 1983 February 10 (Box 39:, Folder 421)
  - pp. 7105 - 7110, 1983 March 11 (Box 39:, Folder 422)
    - Attachments (Box 39:, Folder 423)
  - pp. 7111 - 7115, 1983 April 8 (Box 39:, Folder 424)
  - pp. 7116 - 7123, 1983 May 20 (Box 39:, Folder 425)
    - Attachments (Box 39:, Folder 426 - 427)
    - Attachments (Box 40:, Folder 428)
  - pp. 7124 - 7127, 1983 June 10 (Box 40:, Folder 429)
    - Attachments (Box 40:, Folder 430)
  - pp. 7128 - 7135, 1983 July 8 (Box 40:, Folder 431)
    - Attachments (Box 40:, Folder 432 - 434)
  - pp. 7136 - 7143, 1983 September (Box 41:, Folder 435)
    - Attachments (Box 41:, Folder 436 - 438)
  - 1983 Fall Briefing (Box 41:, Folder 439 - 440)
  - pp. 7144 - 7146, 1983 October 24 (Box 41:, Folder 441)
    - Attachments (Box 41:, Folder 442 - 443)
  - pp. 7147 - 7151, 1983 November (Box 42:, Folder 444)
    - Attachments (Box 42:, Folder 445 - 447)
  - pp. 7152 - 7157, 1984 January 13 (Box 42:, Folder 448)
    - Attachments (Box 42:, Folder 449 - 450)
  - pp. 7158 - 7161, 1984 February 10 (Box 42:, Folder 451)
    - Attachments (Box 42:, Folder 452)
  - 1984 March 9 (Box 43:, Folder 453)
    - Attachments (Box 43:, Folder 454 - 456)
  - pp. 7162 - 7163, 1984 April 4 (Box 43:, Folder 457)
    - Attachments (Box 43:, Folder 458 - 459)
  - pp. 7164 - 7171, 1984 April 13 (Box 43:, Folder 460)
    - Attachments (Box 43:, Folder 461 - 462)
    - Attachments (Box 44:, Folder 463)
  - pp. 7172 - 7179, 1984 May 11 (Box 44:, Folder 464)
    - Attachments (Box 44:, Folder 465 - 466)
  - pp. 7180 - 7182, 1984 June 8 (Box 44:, Folder 467)
    - Attachments (Box 44:, Folder 468 - 470)
  - pp. 7183 - 7190, 1984 July 13 (Box 45:, Folder 471)
    - Attachments (Box 45:, Folder 472 - 475)
  - pp. 7191 - 7196, 1984 September (Box 45:, Folder 476)
    - Attachments (Box 45:, Folder 477 - 478)
  - pp. 7197 - 7199, 1984 October 26 (Box 46:, Folder 479)
    - Attachments (Box 46:, Folder 480 - 481)
  - pp. 7200 - 7204, 1984 November 9 (Box 46:, Folder 482)
    - Attachments (Box 46:, Folder 483 - 485)
  - pp. 7205 - 7207, 1984 December 26 (Box 47:, Folder 486)
    - Attachments (Box 47:, Folder 487 - 488)
  - pp. 7208 - 7213, 1985 January 11 (Box 47:, Folder 489)
    - Attachments (Box 47:, Folder 490 - 493)
  - pp. 7214 - 7216, 1985 February 8 (Box 48:, Folder 494)
    - Attachments (Box 48:, Folder 495 - 497)
  - pp. 7217 - 7223, 1985 March 8 (Box 48:, Folder 498)
    - Attachments (Box 48:, Folder 499 - 501)
  - pp. 7224 - 7228, 1985 April 19 (Box 48:, Folder 502)
    - Attachments (Box 48:, Folder 503 - 504)
    - Attachments (Box 49:, Folder 505 - 506)
  - pp. 7229 - 7232, 1985 May 10 (Box 49:, Folder 507)
    - Attachments (Box 49:, Folder 508 - 510)
  - pp. 7233 - 7234, 1985 May 28 (Box 49:, Folder 511)
    - Attachments (Box 49:, Folder 512)
  - pp. 7235 - 7237, 1985 June 7 (Box 49:, Folder 513)
    - Attachments (Box 49:, Folder 514)
  - pp. 7238 - 7241, 1985 June 14 (Box 50:, Folder 515)
    - Attachments (Box 50:, Folder 516 - 517)
  - pp. 7242 - 7248, 1985 July 12 (Box 50:, Folder 518)
    - Attachments (Box 50:, Folder 519 - 521)
  - pp. 7249 - 7253, 1985 September 13 (Box 51:, Folder 522)
    - Attachments (Box 51:, Folder 523 - 525)
  - pp. 7451 - 7253, 1985 October 11 (Box 51:, Folder 526)
    - Attachments (Box 51:, Folder 527 - 528)
  - pp. 7254 - 7259, 1985 November 8 (Box 51:, Folder 529)
    - Attachments (Box 51:, Folder 530 - 531)
    - Attachments (Box 52:, Folder 532)
  - pp. 7260 - 7266, 1986 January 10 (Box 52:, Folder 533)
    - Attachments (Box 52:, Folder 534 - 536)
  - 1986 February (Box 52:, Folder 537)
    - Attachments (Box 52:, Folder 538 - 539)
  - pp. 7269 - 7275, 1986 March 14 (Box 53:, Folder 540)
    - Attachments (Box 53:, Folder 541 - 544)
  - pp. 7276 - 7280, 1986 April 11 (Box 53:, Folder 545)
    - Attachments (Box 53:, Folder 546 - 548)
  - pp. 7281 - 7287, 1986 May 9 (Box 54:, Folder 549)
    - Attachments (Box 54:, Folder 550 - 554)
  - pp. 7288 - 7290, 1986 June 13 (Box 54:, Folder 555)
    - Attachments (Box 54:, Folder 556 - 557)
  - pp. 7291 - 7300, 1986 July 11 (Box 55:, Folder 558)
    - Attachments (Box 55:, Folder 559 - 561)
  - pp. 7301 - 7309, 1986 September 5 (Box 55:, Folder 562)
    - Attachments (Box 55:, Folder 563 - 564)
  - pp. 7310 - 7313, 1986 October 10 (Box 56:, Folder 565)
    - Attachments (Box 56:, Folder 566 - 567)
  - pp. 7314 - 7321, 1986 November 14 (Box 56:, Folder 568)
    - Attachments (Box 56:, Folder 569 - 571)
  - pp. 7322 - 7327, 1987 January 9 (Box 57:, Folder 572)
    - Attachments (Box 57:, Folder 573 - 575)
  - pp. 7328 - 7331, 1987 February 13 (Box 57:, Folder 576)
    - Attachments (Box 57:, Folder 577 - 579)
  - pp. 7332 - 7341, 1987 March 13 (Box 58:, Folder 580)
    - Attachments (Box 58:, Folder 581 - 584)
  - pp. 7342 - 7349, 1987 April 10 (Box 58:, Folder 585)
    - Attachments (Box 58:, Folder 586 - 587)
  - pp. 7350 - 7358, 1987 May 8 (Box 59:, Folder 588)
    - Attachments (Box 59:, Folder 589 - 591)
  - pp. 7359 - 7365, 1987 June 5 (Box 59:, Folder 592)
    - Attachments (Box 59:, Folder 593 - 594)
  - pp. 7366 - 7373, 1987 July 10 (Box 60:, Folder 595)
    - Attachments (Box 60:, Folder 596 - 600)
  - pp. 7374 - 7382, 1987 September 13 (Box 60:, Folder 601)
    - Attachments (Box 60:, Folder 602)
    - Attachments (Box 61:, Folder 603 - 604)
  - pp. 7383 - 7389, 1987 October 9 (Box 61:, Folder 605)
    - Attachments (Box 61:, Folder 606 - 608)
  - pp. 7390 - 7397, 1987 November 13 (Box 61:, Folder 609)
    - Attachments (Box 61:, Folder 610)
    - Attachments (Box 62:, Folder 611 - 612)
  - pp. 7398 - 7406, 1988 January 8 (Box 62:, Folder 613)
    - Attachments (Box 62:, Folder 614 - 616)
  - pp. 7407 - 7411, 1988 February (Box 63:, Folder 617)
    - Attachments (Box 63:, Folder 618 - 620)
  - pp. 7411 - 7418, 1988 March 11 (Box 63:, Folder 621)
    - Attachments (Box 63:, Folder 622 - 624)
  - pp. 7419 - 7430, 1988 April 8 (Box 64:, Folder 625)
    - Attachments (Box 64:, Folder 626 - 628)
  - pp. 7431 - 7439, 1988 May 13 (Box 64:, Folder 629)
    - Attachments (Box 64:, Folder 630 - 631)
    - Attachments (Box 65:, Folder 632)
  - pp. 7440 - 7445, 1988 June 10 (Box 65:, Folder 633)
    - Attachments (Box 65:, Folder 634 - 635)
  - (p. 7446 - 7454, 1988 July 15 (Box 65:, Folder 636)
    - Attachments (Box 65:, Folder 637 - 641)
    - Attachments (Box 66:, Folder 642 - 643)
  - pp. 7455 - 7461, 1988 September 15 (Box 66:, Folder 644)
    - Attachments (Box 66:, Folder 645 - 647)
  - pp. 7461 - 7468, 1988 October 14 (Box 67:, Folder 648)
    - Attachments (Box 67:, Folder 649 - 650)
  - pp. 7469 - 7477, 1988 November 10 (Box 67:, Folder 651)
    - Attachments (Box 67:, Folder 652 - 654)
  - 1988 December 20 (Box 68:, Folder 655)
    - Attachments (Box 68:, Folder 656 - 660)
  - pp. 7478 - 7485, 1989 January 13 (Box 68:, Folder 661)
    - Attachments (Box 68:, Folder 662 - 663)
  - pp. 7486 - 7492, 1989 February 10 (Box 69:, Folder 664)
    - Attachments (Box 69:, Folder 665 - 666)
  - pp. 7493 - 7498, 1989 March 10 (Box 69:, Folder 667)
    - Attachments (Box 69:, Folder 668 - 669)
  - pp. 7499 - 7506, 1989 April 14 (Box 69:, Folder 670)
    - Attachments (Box 69:, Folder 671 - 672)
  - pp. 7507 - 7513, 1989 May 12 (Box 70:, Folder 673)
    - Attachments (Box 70:, Folder 674)
  - pp. 7514 - 7522, 1989 June16 (Box 70:, Folder 675)
    - Attachments (Box 70:, Folder 676 - 677)
  - pp. 7523 - 7529, 1989 July 14 (Box 71:, Folder 678)
    - Attachments (Box 71:, Folder 679 - 681)
  - pp. 7530 - 7540, 1989 September 15 (Box 71:, Folder 682)
    - Attachments (Box 72:, Folder 683 - 685)
  - pp. 7541 - 7548, 1989 October 13 (Box 72:, Folder 686)
    - Attachments (Box 72:, Folder 687 - 688)
  - pp. 7549 - 7556, 1989 November 17 (Box 73:, Folder 689)
    - Attachments (Box 73:, Folder 690 - 692)
  - pp. 7557 - 7563, 1990 January 12 (Box 73:, Folder 693)
    - Attachments (Box 73:, Folder 694)
    - Attachments (Box 74:, Folder 695 - 696)
  - pp. 7564 - 7568, 1990 February 9 (Box 74:, Folder 697)
    - Attachments (Box 74:, Folder 698 - 699)
  - pp. 7569 - 7573, 1990 March 2 (Box 74:, Folder 700)
    - Attachments (Box 74:, Folder 701)
    - Attachments (Box 75:, Folder 702)
  - pp. 7574 - 7575, 1990 March 16 (Box 75:, Folder 703)
  - 1990 April 3 (Box 75:, Folder 704)
    - Attachments (Box 75:, Folder 705)
  - pp. 7576 - 7583, 20 April 1990 (Box 75:, Folder 706)
    - Attachments (Box 75:, Folder 707 - 708)
  - pp. 7584 - 7592, 1990 May 11 (Box 76:, Folder 709)
    - Attachments (Box 76:, Folder 710 - 711)
  - pp. 7593 - 7596, 1990 June 8 (Box 76:, Folder 712)
    - Attachments (Box 76:, Folder 713 - 714)
  - Budget and Finance, 1990 June 15 (Box 77:, Folder 715)
  - 1990 June 19 (Box 77:, Folder 716)
  - pp. 7597 - 7607, 1990 July 13 (Box 77:, Folder 717)
    - Attachments (Box 77:, Folder 718 - 719)
  - 1990 August 2 (Box 78:, Folder 720)
    - Attachments (Box 78:, Folder 721)
  - 1990 August 23 (Box 78:, Folder 722)
  - pp. 7608 - 7614, 1990 September 14 (Box 78:, Folder 723)
  - pp. 7615 - 7621, 1990 October 12 (Box 78:, Folder 724)
  - pp. 7622 - 7628, 1990 November 9 (Box 78:, Folder 725)
  - pp. 7629 - 7630, 1990 December 10 (Box 78:, Folder 726)
  - pp. 7631 - 7639, 1991 January 11 (Box 78:, Folder 727)
  - pp. 7640 - 7644, 1991 February 8 (Box 79:, Folder 728)
  - pp. 7645 - 7652, 1991 March 6 (Box 79:, Folder 729)
  - pp. 7653 - 7661, 1991 April 5 (Box 79:, Folder 730)
  - pp. 7662 - 7671, 1991 May 10 (Box 79:, Folder 731)
    - Attachments (Box 79:, Folder 732 - 733)
  - pp. 7672 - 7677, 1991 June 14 (Box 79:, Folder 734)
  - pp. 7678 - 7688, 1991 July 12 (Box 80:, Folder 735)
    - Attachments (Box 80:, Folder 736)
  - pp. 7689 - 7696, 1991 September 13 (Box 80:, Folder 737)
    - Attachments (Box 80:, Folder 738 - 739)
  - pp. 7697 - 7703, 1991 October 11 (Box 80:, Folder 740)
    - Attachments (Box 80:, Folder 741)
  - pp. 7704 - 7710, 1991 November 8 (Box 80:, Folder 742)
    - Attachments (Box 80:, Folder 743)
    - Attachments (Box 81:, Folder 744)
  - pp. 7711 - 7721, 1992 January 10 (Box 81:, Folder 745)
    - Attachments (Box 81:, Folder 746 - 749)
  - pp. 7722 - 7735, 1992 February 14 (Box 81:, Folder 750)
    - Attachments (Box 81:, Folder 751 - 752)
  - pp. 7736 - 7744, 1992 March 20 (Box 82:, Folder 753)
    - Attachments (Box 82:, Folder 754 - 757)
  - pp. 7745 - 7753, 1992 April 10 (Box 82:, Folder 758)
    - Attachments (Box 82:, Folder 759 - 762)
  - pp. 7754 - 7755, 1992 May 1 (Box 83:, Folder 763)
  - pp. 7756 - 7762, 1992 May 8 (Box 83:, Folder 764)
    - Attachments (Box 83:, Folder 765 - 768)
  - pp. 7763 - 7769, 1992 June 12 (Box 83:, Folder 769)
    - Attachments (Box 83:, Folder 770 - 772)
    - Attachments (Box 84:, Folder 773)
  - Budget and Finance, 1992 June 25 (Box 84:, Folder 774)
  - pp. 7770 - 7780, 1992 July (Box 84:, Folder 775)
    - Attachments (Box 84:, Folder 776 - 779)
  - (p. 7780, 1992 August 27 (Box 84:, Folder 780)
    - Attachments (Box 84:, Folder 781)
  - pp. 7781 - 7788, 1992 September 11 (Box 84:, Folder 782)
    - Attachments (Box 84:, Folder 783 - 784)
    - Attachments (Box 85:, Folder 785 - 786)
  - pp. 7789 - 7795, 1992 October 9 (Box 85:, Folder 787)
    - Attachments (Box 85:, Folder 788 - 789)
  - pp. 7795 - 7802, 1992 November 13 (Box 85:, Folder 790)
    - Attachments (Box 85:, Folder 791 - 793)
    - Attachments (Box 86:, Folder 794 - 795)
  - pp. 7803 - 7810, 1993 January 8 (Box 86:, Folder 796)
    - Attachments (Box 86:, Folder 797 - 799)
  - pp. 7811 - 7820, 1993 Februaryruary 19 (Box 86:, Folder 800)
    - Attachments (Box 86:, Folder 801 - 802)
    - Attachments (Box 87:, Folder 803 - 804)
  - pp. 7821 - 7827, 1993 Marchch 19 (Box 87:, Folder 805)
    - Attachments (Box 87:, Folder 806 - 808)
  - pp. 7831 - 7837, 1993 Aprilil 16 (Box 87:, Folder 809)
    - Attachments (Box 87:, Folder 810)
    - Attachments (Box 88:, Folder 811)
  - pp. 7837 - 7842, 1993 May 14 (Box 88:, Folder 812)
    - Attachments (Box 88:, Folder 813 - 815)
  - pp. 7843 - 7848, 1993 Junee 11 (Box 88:, Folder 816)
    - Attachments (Box 88:, Folder 817 - 819)
    - Attachments (Box 89:, Folder 820)
  - pp. 7849 - 7857, 1993 July 9 (Box 89:, Folder 821)
    - Attachments (Box 89:, Folder 822 - 825)
  - pp. 7858 - 7866, 1993 September 10 (Box 89:, Folder 826)
    - Attachments (Box 89:, Folder 827 - 828)
    - Attachments (Box 90:, Folder 829 - 830)
  - pp. 7867 - 7872, 1993 October 8 (Box 90:, Folder 831)
    - Attachments (Box 90:, Folder 832 - 833)
  - pp. 7873 - 7882, 1993 November 12 (Box 90:, Folder 834)
    - Attachments (Box 90:, Folder 835 - 836)
    - Attachments (Box 91:, Folder 837 - 838)
  - pp. 7883 - 7893, 1994 February 11 (Box 91:, Folder 839)
    - Attachments (Box 91:, Folder 840 - 842)
  - pp. 7894 - 7901, 1994 Aprilil 8 (Box 91:, Folder 843)
    - Attachments (Box 91:, Folder 844)
    - Attachments (Box 92:, Folder 845 - 846)
  - pp. 7902 - 7911, 1994 May 13 (Box 92:, Folder 847)
    - Attachments (Box 92:, Folder 848 - 849)
  - pp. 7912 - 7919, 1994 Junee 10 (Box 92:, Folder 850)
    - Attachments (Box 92:, Folder 851)
  - pp. 7920 - 7934, 1994 July 15 (Box 92:, Folder 852)
    - Attachments (Box 92:, Folder 853 - 854)
    - Attachments (Box 93:, Folder 855)
  - pp. 7935 - 7937, 1994 August 19 (Box 93:, Folder 856)
  - pp. 7938 - 7946, 1994 September 9 (Box 93:, Folder 857)
  - pp. 7947 - 7955, 1994 October 14 (Box 93:, Folder 858)
    - Attachments (Box 93:, Folder 859 - 860)
  - (p. 7956, 1994 November 3 (Box 93:, Folder 861)
    - Attachments (Box 93:, Folder 862 - 864)
  - pp. 7957 - 7963, 1994 November 11 (Box 93:, Folder 865)
    - Attachments (Box 93:, Folder 866 - 868)
  - pp. 7964 - 7970, 1994 December 9 (Box 94:, Folder 869)
    - Attachments (Box 94:, Folder 870 - 872)
  - pp. 7971 - 7972, 1995 January 9 (Box 94:, Folder 873)
  - pp. 7973 - 7980, 1995 February 10 (Box 94:, Folder 874)
  - pp. 7981 - 7985, 1995 March 8 (Box 94:, Folder 875)
  - pp. 7986 - 7993, 1995 April 21 (Box 94:, Folder 876)
  - pp. 7994 - 7995, 1995 May 19 (Box 94:, Folder 877)
  - pp. 7996 - 8005, 1995 July 14 (Box 94:, Folder 878)
  - pp. 8006 - 8012, 1995 September 8 (Box 95:, Folder 879)
  - 1995 September 27 (Box 95:, Folder 880)
  - pp. 8013 - 8020, 1995 October 13 (Box 95:, Folder 881)
  - pp. 8021 - 8029, 1995 November 10 (Box 95:, Folder 882)
  - pp. 8030 - 8035, 1996 January 12 (Box 95:, Folder 883)
  - pp. 8036 - 8043, 1996 February 9 (Box 95:, Folder 884)
  - pp. 8045 - 8049, 1996 March 15 (Box 95:, Folder 885)
  - pp. 8050 - 8051, 1996 April 2 (Box 95:, Folder 886)
  - pp. 8052 - 8058, 1996 April 12 (Box 95:, Folder 887)
  - pp. 8059 - 8064, 1996 May 10 (Box 96:, Folder 888)
  - (p. 8065, 1996 June 28 (Box 96:, Folder 889)
  - pp. 8066 - 8073, 1996 July 12 (Box 96:, Folder 890)
  - pp. 8074 - 8075, 1996 July 19 (Box 96:, Folder 891)
  - pp. 8076 - 8082, 1996 September 13 (Box 96:, Folder 892)
  - pp. 8083 - 8085, 1996 October 11 (Box 96:, Folder 893)
  - pp. 8086 - 8094, 1996 November 8 (Box 96:, Folder 894)
  - pp. 8095 - 8102, 1997 February 14 (Box 96:, Folder 895)
  - pp. 8103 - 8112, 1997 April 11 (Box 96:, Folder 896)
    - Attachments (Box 97:, Folder 897 - 898)
  - pp. 8113 - 8123, 1997 July 11 (Box 97:, Folder 899)
    - Attachments (Box 97:, Folder 900)
  - pp. 8124 - 8130, 1997 September 26 (Box 98:, Folder 901)
    - Attachments (Box 98:, Folder 902)
  - pp. 8131 - 8139, 1997 October 17 (Box 98:, Folder 903)
    - Attachments (Box 98:, Folder 904)
  - pp. 8140 - 8145, 1997 November 14 (Box 98:, Folder 905)
    - Attachments (Box 98:, Folder 906)
  - pp. 8146 - 8147, 1997 November 21 (Box 99:, Folder 907)
  - pp. 8148 - 8155, 1997 December 12 (Box 99:, Folder 908)
    - Attachments (Box 99:, Folder 909)
  - pp. 8156 - 8166, 1998 February 13 (Box 99:, Folder 910)
    - Attachments (Box 99:, Folder 911)
  - pp. 8167 - 8174, 1998 Aprilil 3 (Box 99:, Folder 912)
    - Attachments (Box 99:, Folder 913)
  - pp. 8175 - 8181, 1998 May 27 (Box 100:, Folder 914)
    - Attachments (Box 100:, Folder 915)
    - Financial Affairs Committee Budget Workshop (Box 100:, Folder 916)
  - Budget Workshop, 1998 July 19 (Box 100:, Folder 917 - 918)
  - Budget Workshop, 1998 July 20 (Box 101:, Folder 919)
  - Budget Workshop—Health Center, 1998 July 19 (Box 101:, Folder 920)
  - pp. 8182 - 8200, 1998 July 20 (Box 101:, Folder 921)
    - Handouts (Box 101:, Folder 922)
    - Attachments (Box 101:, Folder 923)
  - pp. 8201 - 8208, 1998 September 15 (Box 101:, Folder 924)
    - Handouts (Box 101:, Folder 925)
    - Attachments (Box 101:, Folder 926)
  - pp. 8209 - 8218, 1998 November 10 (Box 102:, Folder 927)
    - Attachments (Box 102:, Folder 928 - 929)
  - pp. 8219 - 8220, 1998 December 11 (Box 102:, Folder 930)
  - pp. 8221 - 8233, 1999 February 9 (Box 102:, Folder 931)
    - Attachments (Box 102:, Folder 932 - 933)
  - pp. 8234 - 8244, 1999 April 13 (Box 103:, Folder 934)
    - Letters from the public (Box 103:, Folder 935)
    - Handouts (Box 103:, Folder 936)
    - Attachments (Box 103:, Folder 937)
  - pp. 8245 - 8246, 1999 June 14 (Box 103:, Folder 938)
    - Attachments (Box 103:, Folder 939)
  - pp. 8247 - 8257, 1999 June 25 (Box 103:, Folder 940)
    - Attachments (Box 103:, Folder 941)
  - Budget Workshop, 1999 June 25
    - Handouts (Box 103:, Folder 942 - 944)
    - Workbook (Box 103:, Folder 945)
    - UCHC Operating and Capital Budget Executive Summary (Box 104:, Folder 946)
  - pp. 8258 - 8261, 1999 July 21 (Box 104:, Folder 947)
    - Attachments (Box 104:, Folder 948)
  - pp. 8262 - 8270, 1999 September 21 (Box 104:, Folder 949)
  - pp. 8271 - 8278, 1999 November 16 (Box 104:, Folder 950)
    - Attachments (Box 104:, Folder 951)
  - pp. 8279 - 8284, 1999 December 21 (Box 104:, Folder 952)
    - Agenda and attachments (Box 104:, Folder 953)
    - Handouts (Box 104:, Folder 954)
  - pp. 8285 - 8291, 2000 January 11 (Box 104:, Folder 955)
    - Agenda and attachments (Box 104:, Folder 956)
  - pp. 8292 - 8304, 2000 February 2 (Box 104:, Folder 957)
    - Attachments (Box 104:, Folder 958)
  - pp. 8305 - 8319, 2000 April 11 (Box 105:, Folder 959)
    - Attachments (Box 105:, Folder 960)
  - pp. 8320 - 8326, 2000 May 8 (Box 105:, Folder 961)
    - Attachments (Box 105:, Folder 962)
    - Annual Report on Diversity and Affirmative Action (Box 105:, Folder 963)
    - Operating Plan—Properties Management (Box 105:, Folder 964)
  - pp. 8327 - 8331, 2000 June 29 (Box 105:, Folder 965)
    - Attachments (Box 105:, Folder 966)
    - Budget Workshop, 2000 June (Box 105:, Folder 967)
  - pp. 8332 - 8335, 2000 August 1 (Box 106:, Folder 968)
    - Attachments (Box 106:, Folder 969)
  - pp. 8336 - 8343, 2000 September 12 (Box 106:, Folder 970)
    - Attachments (Box 106:, Folder 971)
    - UConn 2000 Report #10 (Box 106:, Folder 972)
    - Outlying Parcels Master Plan, Final Report, 2000 March (Box 106:, Folder 973)
  - pp. 8344 - 8355, 2000 November 20 (Box 106:, Folder 974)
    - Attachments (Box 106:, Folder 975)
  - pp. 8356 - 8357, 2001 January 24 (Box 107:, Folder 976)
    - Attachments (Box 107:, Folder 977)
  - pp. 8358 - 8360, 2001 February 13 (Box 107:, Folder 978)
    - Attachments (Box 107:, Folder 979)
  - pp. 8361 - 8371, 2001 February 22 (Box 107:, Folder 980)
    - Handouts (Box 107, Folder 981)
  - pp. 8372 - 8373, 2001 March 13 (Box 107:, Folder 982)
  - pp. 8374 - 8391, 2001 April 12 (Box 107:, Folder 983)
    - Attachments (Box 107:, Folder 984)
  - pp. 8392 - 8396, 2001 April 18 (Box 107:, Folder 985)
  - pp.8397 - 8398, 2001 May 8 (Box 107:, Folder 986)
    - Attachments and Agenda (Box 107:, Folder 987)
  - pp. 8399 - 8408, 2001 June 26 (Box 107:, Folder 988)
    - Attachments (Box 107:, Folder 989)
  - pp. 8409 - 8427, 2001 July 24 (Box 108:, Folder 990)
    - Attachments (Box 108:, Folder 991)
  - p. 8428, 2001 August 3 (Box 108:, Folder 992)
  - pp. 8429 - 8442, 2001 September 26 (Box 108:, Folder 993)
    - Attachments (Box 108:, Folder 994)
  - pp. 8443 - 8456, 2001 November 16 (Box 108:, Folder 995)
    - Attachments (Box 108:, Folder 996)
  - pp. 8457 - 8464, 2002 January 18 (Box 108:, Folder 997)
    - Attachments (Box 108:, Folder 998)
  - pp. 8465 - 8469, 2002 February 14 (Box 109:, Folder 999)
  - pp. 8469 - 8470, 2002 April 3 (Box 108:, Folder 1000)
  - pp. 8471 - 8484, 2002 April 16 (Box 108:, Folder 1001)
    - Attachments (Box 108:, Folder 1002)
  - pp. 8485 - 8488, 2002 May 30 (Box 109:, Folder 1003)
    - UConn 2000 Report #14 (Box 109:, Folder 1004)
  - pp. 8489 - 8501, 2002 June 25 (Box 109:, Folder 1005)
    - Attachments (Box 109:, Folder 1006)
  - pp. 8502 - 8520, 2002 August 13 (Box 109:, Folder 1007)
    - Attachments (Box 109:, Folder 1008)
  - pp. 8521 - 8535, 2002 October 1 (Box 110:, Folder 1009)
    - Attachments (Box 109:, Folder 1010)
  - pp. 8536 - 8547, 2002 November 13 (Box 110:, Folder 1011)
    - Attachments (Box 109:, Folder 1012)
  - pp. 8548 - 8568, 2003 January 14 (Box 110:, Folder 1013)
    - Attachments and Handouts (Box 110:, Folder 1014)
  - pp. 8569 - 8571, 2003 March 11 (Box 110:, Folder 1015)
  - pp. 8572 - 8584, 2003 April 15 (Box 110:, Folder 1016)
    - Attachments and Handouts (Box 110:, Folder 1017)
  - pp. 8585 - 8589, 2003 May 7 (Box 111:, Folder 1018)
  - pp. 8590 - 8597, 2003 June 25 (Box 111:, Folder 1019)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1020)
  - pp. 8598 - 8601, 2003 July 22 (Box 111:, Folder 1021)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1022)
  - pp. 8602 - 8611, 2003 August 21 (Box 111:, Folder 1023)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1024)
  - pp. 8612 - 8620, 2003 September 23 (Box 111:, Folder 1025)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1026)
  - pp. 8621 - 8636, 2003 December 2 (Box 111:, Folder 1027)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1028)
  - pp. 8637 - 8661, 2004 March 23 (Box 111:, Folder 1029)
  - pp. 8662 - 8676, 2004 June 22 (Box 111:, Folder 1030)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1031)
  - pp. 8677 - 8688, 2004 August 3 (Box 111:, Folder 1032)
    - Attachments (Box 111:, Folder 1033)
  - pp. 8689 - 8704, 2004 September 8 (Box 112:, Folder 1034)
    - Attachments (Box 112:, Folder 1035)
    - Attachments (Box 112:, Folder 1036)
  - pp. 8705 - 8716, 2004 November 17 (Box 112:, Folder 1037)
    - Attachments (Box 112:, Folder 1038)